Fresh water. Fresh meat.
Swamp Shark is a action, adventure, comedy film directed by Griff Furst.
Open on gorgeous swamplands of the Atchafalaya Basin in the summer.
Lots of beautiful teens are at the beach the weekend before Gator Fest.
That night an animal smuggling deal goes wrong and a large sea
creature escapes into a swampy backwoods river.
At the McDaniel's "Gator Shack" restaurant, a local,
Jackson is drunk, and gets mangled to bits.
The town sheriff blames the carnage on the McDaniel's "escaped"
pack of gators and tries hauling them off to jail.
Rachel McDaniel, head of the family, claims to have seen the fin of a shark!
Rachel and her family, along with the help of a mysterious stranger, Charlie, take on the Swampshark and the law to clear their names, save Rachel's kid sister
Krystal and prevent the unwitting folks at the upcoming Gator Fest from being torn to shreds by a beast the likes of which no one has ever seen!
Rachel McDaniel, played by Kristy Swanson.
Sheriff Watson, played by Robert Davi.
Charlie, played by D. B. Sweeney.
Deputy Stanley, played by Wade Boggs.
Krystal, played by Sophie Sinise.
Martin, played by Jason Rogel.
Swamp Shark is a 2011 low budget American thriller film directed
by Griff Furst and starring Kristy Swanson, D.
Sweeney, Robert Davi, Jason Rogel, Sophia Sinise, Richard Tanne, and Jeff Chase.
The film was produced by Kenneth M.
Badish and Daniel Lewis and was written by Eric
Miller, Charles Bolon, and Jennifer Iwen.
It is a Syfy Channel original picture which premiered in the U.S.
on the Syfy Channel on June 25, 2011.
The film explores themes of sheriff, shark attack, louisiana, swamp, bikini.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.